NURUL BALQIS ABD RAHMAN

(+60)18-9844762

nurulblqs99@gmail.com

Yong Peng, Johor

BSc (Hons) Information Technology in Computer Application Development

ABOUT ME

IT graduate with proven programming and communication skills. Successfully producing several projects through the course of diploma and degree. I enjoy learning through the challenges when being assigned the responsibility to execute the projects. I hope to become an experienced web developer in the next 3 years.

Personal Strengths:

- Highly committed in work especially with time constraint tasks.
- Able to converse verbally and written in both English and Malay.
- A highly effective team player and adaptive to various workplace environments.
- Flexible and agile with changing tasks, and a fast learner.

EXPERIENCE

Support Technician (Part Time) Fei Yue Communication Trading

November 2023 - Jan 2024

IT Support (Intern)

KPTM SDN. BHD. Headquarter May 2023 - August 2023

IT Intern

Teraju Sama SDN. BHD. *November 2019 - March 2020*

Part Time Baker and Attendant

Bin Bakery *March 2017 - 2020*

Part Time Waitress

North Station Bistro *January 2017 - Feb 2017*

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honours) in Computer Application Development

Universiti Poly-Tech Malaysia 2020 - 2023

Diploma in Information Technology

Kolej Poly-Tech Mara Batu Pahat 2017 - 2020

Pure Science Stream (SPM)

Maktab Rendah Sains Mara Batu Pahat 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

Programming Language

- PHP
- HTML5
- JavaScript
- Laravel (basic)
- CSS
- MySQL

Web & Multimedia

- Website Design
- Video Editing
- Video Photomontages
- Web Application

Interpersonal

- Communications
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Flexibility
- Responsibility

REFERENCE